Volunteering is a significant life experience for any high school student studying in BC, Canada
ボランティアは、ブリティッシュコロンビア州の高校生にとって重要な経験となります
It is not only a part of the graduation requirement,
卒業要件の一部にもなっています
but it's also an opportunity for your child to develop characteristics such as:
また、ボランティア活動を通じ、あなたの子供が
compassion, resiliency and self motivation  to gain understanding of oneself and others
自分自身や他人の理解を深めるための思いやり、モチベーション
to build new friendships and network with the local community
地域社会とのかかわりや、新しい友情とネットワークを作るとても有意義な機会となります
and also to create a sense of belonging in their new environment.
また、彼らが学校以外の新しいカナダの環境と繋がることにもなります
At Bodwell High School we understand the importance of this area of life learning
ボドウェル高校でも、この分野を重要視し、奨励しています
and the challenges our students may encounter given that they have no direct connections here.
ボランティア活動と一言でいっても、中々、個人で探す事は難しい為、
Therefore an extensive support system and programs have been developed
ボドウェルには、支援システムとプログラムがあります
for students to sign up and participate during weekdays and weekends.
学生たちは、ボランティア活動へプログラムを通じサインアップして参加が可能です
There are individual and group volunteering opportunities that are available for all students to sign up
すべての学生対象となりｄ、個人でのボランティアと、グループでののボランティアの機会があります
and are mentored by school staff
また、学校スタッフの指導のもと、行われている
Students interested in campus jobs and school activities are individually recruited
キャンパス内の仕事、学校での活動、などは個別に募集がかかます
and selected through a brief interview process.
そのようなボランティアは、インタビューを行い対象生徒が選ばれます
As for the group volunteer opportunities,
グループボランティアは、
there are many chances for students to join  local festivals
地元のイベントに参加するなど、機会は沢山あります
to volunteer and help out and to learn their cultures; like this one.
現地の文化をボランティアを通じ、学ぶことができます
For off-campus community volunteer opportunities,
このような、学校外のコミュニティのボランティアへの参加は
the newly designed signup systems allow students to sign up online in their own time
学生ポータルアカウントにアクセスし
by accessing their student portal account.
サインアップシステムを使って、オンラインでサインアップすることが可能です
We have also incorporated volunteer opportunities into our Saturday E and after-school clubs.
また、土曜クラスや放課後のクラブにも、ボランティア活動があります
By checking in with the parent portal my child website and student portal
ボドウェルのペアレンツポータルにチェックインすることで、
both parents and students are able to monitor what students have accomplished during their stay in Bodwell.
保護者も、生徒の学習・生活の様子をオンラインで確認することが可能です
They are able to track a student's experience, not only academically,
受講している科目のテストの結果や、学生のボランティア活動の時間なども確認できます
but also maintain a record of participation in students life skill building activities.
また、学生の寮での生活の様子なども、ご覧いただけます
Student life experience and volunteer work are important for post-secondary application and beyond
課外活動やボランティア活動の内容などは、大学進学の際にも重要になります
It helps your child explore their own sense of self and life direction
また、生徒達が、色々な経験を通じ、自身の生活や今後の方向性を探るのにも役立ちます
At Bodwell, we hope to promote thoughtfulness and provide a meaningful experience through volunteer work.
ボドウェルでは、ボランティア活動を通して思慮深さを促進し、有意義な留学経験を提供したいと考えています